[  {    "question": "What is the capital city of Bangladesh?",    "options": [      "A) Chittagong",      "B) Sylhet",      "C) Dhaka",      "D) Rajshahi"    ],
    "answer": "C) Dhaka"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the longest natural sea beach in the world located in Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Cox's Bazar",
      "B) Kuakata",
      "C) Saint Martin's Island",
      "D) Bakkhali Beach"
    ],
    "answer": "A) Cox's Bazar"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the largest river in Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Brahmaputra",
      "B) Ganges",
      "C) Meghna",
      "D) Jamuna"
    ],
    "answer": "D) Jamuna"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the national animal of Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Bengal tiger",
      "B) Lion",
      "C) Rhinoceros",
      "D) Leopard"
    ],
    "answer": "A) Bengal tiger"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the largest mangrove forest in the world located in Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Sundarbans",
      "B) Bhitarkanika",
      "C) Pichavaram",
      "D) Dandeli-Anshi"
    ],
    "answer": "A) Sundarbans"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the national bird of Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Sparrow",
      "B) Oriental magpie-robin",
      "C) Bulbul",
      "D) Doel"
    ],
    "answer": "D) Doel"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the highest peak in Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Mount Everest",
      "B) K2",
      "C) Kangchenjunga",
      "D) Saka Haphong"
    ],
    "answer": "D) Saka Haphong"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the national fish of Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Ilish",
      "B) Rohu",
      "C) Catfish",
      "D) Tilapia"
    ],
    "answer": "A) Ilish"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the famous festival in Bangladesh that is celebrated to mark the end of the fasting month of Ramadan?",
    "options": [
      "A) Eid al-Fitr",
      "B) Eid al-Adha",
      "C) Ashura",
      "D) Muharram"
    ],
    "answer": "A) Eid al-Fitr"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the national flower of Bangladesh?",
    "options": [
      "A) Lotus",
      "B) Water lily",
      "C) Rose",
      "D) Jasmine"
    ],
    "answer": "B) Water lily"
  }
]
